<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>PowerShell - Tag - Kunj Sangani</title>
        <link>http://example.org/tags/powershell/</link>
        <description>PowerShell - Tag - Kunj Sangani</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>sangani.kunj@gmail.com (Kunj Sangani)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>sangani.kunj@gmail.com (Kunj Sangani)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 21:57:40 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/powershell/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How To Create Portable Modules Using PowerShell In macOS</title>
    <link>http://example.org/2020/07/how-to-create-portable-modules-using-power-shell-in-mac-os/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 21:57:40 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Kunj Sangani</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/2020/07/how-to-create-portable-modules-using-power-shell-in-mac-os/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction With the introduction of PowerShell 7 it is very easy to use PowerShell across all the platforms and so we will want to create our own custom PowerShell modules as well.
To do so it is very easy with the introduction of .net core &ndash; truly Microsoft is being platform agnostic in terms of development.
So let us understand how we can create our own custom module for PowerShell.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>CRUD Operation On SPFx Webpart Using PnP PowerShell</title>
    <link>http://example.org/2020/06/crud-operation-on-share-point-sp-fx-webpart-using-pn-p-power-shell/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 21:57:40 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Kunj Sangani</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/2020/06/crud-operation-on-share-point-sp-fx-webpart-using-pn-p-power-shell/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction With the introduction to SharePoint Framework (SPFx), creating webparts using frontend technologies has been very easy. But what if we want to maintain it and create some automation for adding, updating, or deleting this SPFx webparts? In this scenario, PnP PowerShell helps us with all the CRUD operations for SPFx webparts. So let us check how we can utilize this.
Installation of PnP PowerShell Installing PnP PowerShell is very easy.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
